poorvikamobile.com 2011-05-30

# Mobiles at lowest rate in India. Mobile showroom at Chennai . lowest price on mobile phones accessories, recharge, iPods, Mp3, memory card, Camera, DTH. “Think mobile!.. Think poorvika!... “ Buy branded mobile Nokia mobile, Sony mobile, Samsung mobile, Htc mobile, Blackberry mobile ,Lg mobile at lowest price in India. Buy your favorite mobiles through online purchase. Free home delivery available only at poorvika

|  |   
---  
| **Privacy Policy - General**  
---  
  
We provide these privacy highlights for your convenience but we encourage you to review the full Poorvika mobile world, Chennai, India.  
  
**Collection, Use, Disclosure, and Security of Personal Information**  
  
  * We collect personal information when you use our services or otherwise interact with us, including information you provide, such as contact information, billing & credit information, and resumes; information that is automatically collected, such as details about use of our services and our Web pages; and information from other sources, such as credit reports and mailing lists.

  * We use personal information for various business purposes, such as to complete transactions and bill for products and services; respond to requests for service or assistance; create and improve products and services; suggest additional or different products or service; and protect our rights and property.

  * We do not sell, rent, or provide personal information to unaffiliated third-parties to market their products and services to you. We may disclose personal information to unaffiliated third-parties who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf and under certain other limited circumstances, subject to restrictions on the third-parties’ use of such information.

  * We use a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information and we use reasonable procedures to erase or render it unreadable when we dispose of it.

**Access and Choice**  
  
  * You may access and modify your contact information by visiting poorvikamobile.com, visiting a Poorvika mobile retail store, or by contacting Customer Service.

  * If you are a Poorvika customer and you manage your account online, you can change your marketing preferences by logging into your my Poorvika Profile.

  * If you are a Poorvika customer but do not manage your account online, you can change your marketing preference by completing our customer opt-out form.

  * If you are not a Poorvika customer and would like to opt-out of marketing communications from Poorvika Mobile world, you can do so by completing our non-customer opt-out form

  * You may also manage your marketing preferences by contacting Customer Service. When you dial 43 666 666 or on any phone, the right marketing promotions and instructions will assist by us to you.

**Other Privacy Information**  
  
  * We do not solicit children to purchase our services or products and our Web sites are not designed to attract children under the age of 13.

  * We may use cookies, Web beacons, and similar technologies.
  * Poorvika follows the ISO’s Best Practices Guidelines for Location-Based Services. With your consent, we may provide location-based services or provide access to location information so third-parties may provide you such services.

  * Services and functionality offered through certain Poorvika Mobile devices are provided in conjunction with third parties, in which case personal information from your devices may be uploaded and stored on their servers.

  * When you install third-party applications on your device, you may give your consent for the third party to access certain information you have stored on your device or to access Poorvika network information to facilitate the application’s functions.

**Policy Updates and Contact Information**  
  
  * We may update this policy from time to time and you should refer to it often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes.

  * If we intend to use or disclose personal information in a way that is materially different from that stated in this policy at the time it was collected, we will post notice of the change on our Web site’s home page for at least 30 days before we implement the change and give you an opportunity to opt-out of the proposed use.

  * If you have questions, comments, or concerns about this policy or about Poorvika privacy practices, you may contact us through info@poorvika.com or using the other contact information provided in the full privacy policy.

* * *  
  
**Privacy Policy - PoorvikaSMS**  
  
  * PoorvikaSMS takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

  * What This Privacy Policy Covers? This policy covers how Poorvikasms treats personal information that Poorvikasms collects and receives? Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Information Collection and Use General**  
  
  * Poorvikasms collects personal information when you register with Poorvikasms.

  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email ld, address, birth date, gender, Mobile, Location etc.

  * Poorvikasms automatically receives and records information about every message on our server logos.

  * We Record every Contact you register in your address book.

  * Poorvikasms uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, Providing More value in the form of Inserted ads in every message you send to your contacts.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
  
  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Poorvikasms under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Poorvikasms communicate with you about offers from Poorvika and our marketing partners. However these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person violations of Poorvikasms’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

  * We transfer information about you if Poorvikasms is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Poorvikasms will notify you before information about you are transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  * Poorvikasms displays targeted advertisements based on personal information.

  * Poorvikasms inserts targeted ads in every message (SMS) you send to your contacts. Also you may even receive targeted SMS ads according to your profile.

  * You may receive SMS Advertisements or offers from our Trusted Partners.

* * *
